MOHAMMAD KHEZRI

Junior Web Developer

I consider myself to be a combination of artistic and technological. I enjoy creating, designing and developing web apps and UI. After several years working in graphic design, I decided to expand my experience in field of web application. I believe there is plenty of room to further develop my skills and learn new materials as a web developer.

Contact:

+1- 832-417-9122 khezri@outlook.com www.linkedin.com/in/mohammad-khezri

Portfolio:

www.kezri.com https://github.com/m-khezri

Education:

Full stack C# .Net developer Nashville Software School, 2018

Experience:

Apprentice Software Developer Nashville Software School | Aug 2018 - Present

Intensive part-time software development bootcamp focusing on full stack development fundamentals and problem solving.

- Hands on application of OOP fundamentals and SOLID principles through
- group and individual projects reflecting real world business problems
- Source code version control with Git/GitHub
- JavaScript fundamentals leveraging DRY, modular, readable code and
- reusable components
- Built single-page applications with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript libraries
- like jQuery
- Task Automation with Grunt: Linting with Eslint, module bundling
- Styled applications with CSS Frameworks Bootstrap and wrote custom styles with SASS

Art Director and graphic designer, 2004-2017 Mazinoor Lighting Industries Inc | 2004 - 2017

As an art director, I was responsible to lead a team of creative to design variety of design materials and web design

- Project management and team leading
- Communicated with ICT department in order to effectively create website graphics
- Acted as a prepress color management specialist and supervised offset and digital printing
- Designed and supervised production of products manuals, pricelist booklets, commercial magazines, office stationary, label and package design, convention advertising products, etc., using Adobe Illustrator and Adobe InDesign
- Created videography, project/ product photography using full-frame DSLR cameras for 100+ projects

Advertising Agency Founder Charkhaneh Advertising Agency | 2008 – 2010

Established an online advertising agency to help small businesses to advertise and sale their products online.

- Developed and operated an advertising website to help small businesses sell products online
- Designed, printed and distributed advertising magazines, billboards, catalogs to various businesses
- Performed commercial photography for resorts, hotels, and restaurants